(トビ)あれれ 先輩！
あんな所に団子屋がありますよ！
Oh, Senpai!
Over there...
There's a dango shop!
Let's take a break.
ちょっと休憩しましょうよ～。
We've been walking all day.
I'm exhausted!
You don't look exhausted at all.
Why are you so easygoing?
ったく のんきなヤツだ。
But Senpai, we're trying to
catch a Tailed Beast,
yet we don't even know where it is.
どこにいるのさえ
わからないんだから。
So let's just take it easy.
そういえば
何 捕まえるんでしたっけ？
By the way,
what are we going to catch again?
Three-Tails! Three-Tails!
One-Tail, Two-Tails...
一尾 ニ尾 ボクはトビ！ なんちって！
And I'm Tobi! Duh!
Here's dango for you.
Wow! It looks yummy!
Let's see...
お～！ うまそうだなぁ！
どれどれ～？
いただきま～す！
Munch time!
Man, it's so good!
This sauce is really good.
これは いいタレだ ハハッ！
甘すぎず辛すぎず。
It's not too sweet, nor too salty.
It's a masterpiece!
ん～！ 絶品ですよ これ！
あ～ おいしかった。
Ahh... It was great.
Oh, Senpai, Senpai. Look at that!
Huh?
That looks exactly like your work, doesn't it?
Could it be that your work is...
a rip-off?
You...!
(デイダラ)テメエ！
ギッ！
だぁ～っ！
I'm going to kill you!
(トビ)あ～れ～！
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
explain to me this happiness
anata ga saikin taiken shita
that you just got to experience?
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka
or maybe you're so blessed
megumare sugite ite
that you can't even remember it
omoidasenai kamo
that you stand here now
ima koko ni iru koto
that you still live and breathe
iki wo shite iru koto
I realised that they all were miracles
tada soredake no koto ga
just by themselves
kiseki da to kidzuku
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
you know the closer you get to something
the tougher it is to see it
and i'll never take it for granted
it's fine to say you'll never give up
oi tsudzukete kita yume
and to keep chasing your dreams
akiramezu ni susumeyo nante
but the more time you spend talking big
kirei goto wo ieru hodo
the less you get done
nanimo dekicha inai kedo
I will press that handful of courage against my heart
hito nigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
and with its help survive another day
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and i'll never take it for granted
let's go
The Rampaging Tailed Beast
(牛頭)こ… これは!?
Th-This is...
(紅蓮)現れるよ 三尾が！
The Three-Tails is about to appear!
What's this feeling...?
What's the matter, Shino?
My insects... feel a weird Chakra.
Weird Chakra?
これまでに
感じたことがないような➡
They've never felt so much Chakra before.
膨大な量のチャクラだ。
(赤丸)ワン！
どうやら赤丸も お前の蟲と
同じものを感じてるようだぜ！
It looks like Akamaru feels
the same thing as your insects!
Then it must be there!
Let's hurry up.
(麟児)この感じ… この
ビリビリと空気を伝うような殺気…➡
This feeling... It's like highly charged air
and a frantic feeling...
木ノ葉のヤツら… じゃねえ。
This isn't from the guys
from the Hidden Leaf.
(麒児)何が起きてるんだ!?
What's happening?
Right there?!
What the hell is that?
A fog...?
(ヤマト)コウモリは
あの霧に向かって行ったようだね。
It looks like the bats are flying
toward the fog.
間違いない。 膨大なチャクラも
あそこから出ている。
No question about it!
A huge amount of Chakra
is coming from over there.
あの霧の中に いるってことか？
Is it inside that fog?
Yes, but we can't identify it.
あそこに突っ込んでみれば
わかるってばよ！
Let's dive in and find out!
まぁ そう焦るな…。
覚悟を決めるか。
Hey, slow down.
Let's get ready first.
ヘッ そうこなくっちゃ！
Heh! That's what I wanted to hear!
全員 戦闘準備！
しかし ムチャはするな。
Everyone, prepare for action!
But don't rush!
(シノ/キバ)了解！
ワン！
- Roger!
了解だってばよ！
Understood!
They're increasing in number.
援軍を呼んだか？
Did they call for reinforcements?
なんか
見つかりまくりなんだけど！
I think they can easily see us!
かまわん！ 一気に突っ込む！
It doesn't matter!
Let's drop in!
We're at a disadvantage number-wise.
ここは 紅蓮さんたちが戻るまで
時間稼ぎをするぞ。
Let's buy some time until
Guren gets here!
キホウ 煙幕をはれ！
(キホウ)あぁ 了解した。
Kihou, lay a smoke screen!
Understood.
カカシ先輩！
Kakashi-senpai!
A smoke screen...
They're lying in wait for us.
ここで時間を食えば➡
But if we stay here too long,
湖で何が起きているのか
探れなくなる可能性もある。
we won't be able to find out
what's happening at the lake.
二手に分かれるか…。
We should split into two groups...
ナルト お前は別行動だ。
え？ オレってば 戦わないのか？
Naruto, you go by yourself.
What?! I'm not attacking?
Our main mission is to research the lake.
Oh, that's right...
We'll create a diversion and
you head off to the center of the lake.
だが 戦闘は禁止だ。
あぁ わかった！
But don't attack.
Yes, understood.
Are you sure? Only Naruto...?
Let's show him a bit of trust.
《生き抜くことに関して
ナルトより勝負強いヤツはいない。
No one is a better survivor than Naruto.
頼むぞ ナルト。
Good luck, Naruto.
You're definitely
the Number One Unpredictable Ninja
in the Hidden Leaf.
反応がない。 誰もいないようだ。
No reaction...
It looks like nobody's here.
(カカシ)行くぞ！
Let's go!
(キバ)クソッ… なんも見えねえ。
Damn it! I can't see anything.
逃げたんでしょうか？
Did they escape already?
時間稼ぎかもしれん
油断するな！
They must be buying time.
Keep your guard up!
よし このへんからなら…！
All right, I think from here...
一気に湖に突っ込むってばよ！
I'm going to head into
the lake!
突っ込みすぎた…。
(ガマ竜)フフ おやつね。
I went in too deep...
Snack for me.
(ガマ吉)ったく 帰ったと思ったら
呼び出しおって！
Hey, right after we got home,
you called us over here!
ガマ使いが荒いのう オメエも！
You're such a toad driver!
Come on, I'll give you something in return.
しかし この強烈なチャクラ。
But, this intense Chakra...
I wonder what's behind the fog?
霧の向こうに
何がおるっちゅうんじゃ…。
(カブト)来るぞ！
It's coming!
これが三尾…。
This is the Three-Tails...
想像以上だ。
It's more than we expected...
なんだ？ この威圧感…。
What is this? This intimidation...!
(カブト)やった！ 成功だ！
We did it... It was a success.
幽鬼丸が三尾をコントロールしている！
Yuukimaru is controlling the Three-Tails!
うわ～！
幽鬼丸！
Yuukimaru!
まずい！ これ以上
力を使い続ければ…。
Damn! If he keeps using his power...!
(紅蓮)コイツが倒れたら
三尾は どうなる？
If he fails,
what will happen to the Three-Tails?
それを抑え込むのが
お前の役目だ！
Your job is to stop that from happening!
チッ！
《カブト : 幽鬼丸の力でも
三尾を抑えられないのか…》
Even Yuukimaru's power can't control
the Three-Tails...!
Yuukimaru!
何だってばよ!? この声は。
What's that sound?!
紅蓮 早く コイツの動きを封じろ！
Guren!
Stop this beast immediately!
いちいち命令するな！
Stop being so bossy!
《コイツ 図体のわりに
動きが早い！》
This beast!
Although he's huge, he's quick!
今のうちに！
Right now!
(紅蓮)牛頭！
(牛頭)早く！
Gozu!
Hurry!
(牛頭)うわぁ！
Crystal Style! Divine Pathway Jutsu!
どうだ！
There!
私の水晶が砕けた!?
My crystal shattered?!
チッ 結晶！ 巨大六角手裏剣！
Giant! Crystal Hexagonal Shuriken!
This is so hard!
Muddy turtle!
≪(カブト)紅蓮 何やってる！
三尾を殺すつもりか!?
Guren! What are you doing?
Are you trying to kill the Three-Tails?!
Contain him! Or we'll all die!
≪ヤツを封じ込めろ！
出来なければ 全滅するぞ！
《でかい術には それなりの
準備ってのがいるんだよ！》
Large-scale Jutsu need preparation!
《間に合わない！》
It's too late!
《牛頭！》
Gozu...!
Hurry...
晶遁！ 水晶壁 八の陣！
Crystal Style!
Crystal Wall, 8th Formation!
(紅蓮)食らえ！ カメ野郎！
Eat this, turtle bastard!
She did it...!
《晶遁… 紅蓮に
ここまで力があったとは》
Crystal Style...
I never knew Guren
had this much ability...
(紅蓮)ハァ ハァ… チャクラを…
使いすぎたか… ハァ ハァ…。
I used a bit too much... Chakra...
おい シノ 寄ってくんなよ。
Hey Shino,
don't get too close to me!
(シノ)別に お前に
寄っているわけではない。
I wouldn't get too close to you.
Then why did your shoulder brush
against me?!
(シノ)なぜなら オレたちの円陣が
小さくなっているからだ。
Because our circle is getting small.
ムダ口をたたくな！
Keep your mouth shut!
Focus on finding the enemy.
敵がどこにいるか
集中するんだ。
でもよぉ カカシ先生！
But, Kakashi-sensei!
(ヒナタ)上です 気をつけて。
Above us! Watch out!
《奇襲は失敗か》
Our ambush failed!
(サクラ)カカシ先生！
Kakashi-sensei!
サクラ サイ 助かったぞ。
Thanks Sakura, Sai.
Hinata, are you better already?
(シノ)それにしても よく…。
Yeah!
But still, how did she...?
(シノ)そうか 白眼か。
I see, her Byakugan...
We'd better be careful with
that little girl's Jutsu.
煙幕のなかだろうが
オレたちの居場所がバレちまう クソッ》
Even if we were in a smoke screen,
she would find us...
Damn it!
なんだ ここ？
波ひとつ立っとらんのぉ。
What kind of place is this?!
There's not one wave,
and no sign of fish.
魚の気配も まったくしない。
不気味じゃ。
It's really weird...
何か見えてきたぞ。
I see something.
(ガマ竜)ああ カメさんだ。
カメさんがいるよ。
Oh! It's a turtle!
There's a turtle inside!
(ガマ竜)兄ちゃん
なんだろうね このカメさん？
Brother! What kind of turtle is this?
ナ ナルト コイツは尾獣じゃ。
尾獣？
N-Naruto, th-this is a Tailed Beast!
(ガマ吉)じゃけん 三尾じゃ！
Tailed Beast?
Yeah! It's the Three-Tails!
ウゥ…。
三尾？
Three-Tails...?
(三尾)オォ…。
オォ～ッ！
《あれだけの術でも
止められないのか》
Even that huge Jutsu couldn't stop it?!
紅蓮 幽鬼丸を連れて逃げろ。
牛頭 お前もだ。
Guren! Take Yuukimaru and run!
Gozu! You, too!
牛頭 幽鬼丸を守れ！
わかりました。
Gozu, protect Yuukimaru!
All right!
紅蓮さん。
Guren...!
お前の相手は 私だよ！ ハアッ！
You fight with me!
アイツは！
She's...!
なんで アイツが三尾と？
Why is she fighting with the Three-Tails?!
ヤァ～ッ！
紅蓮さん！
Guren!
なんで お前がここに？
What are you doing here...?!
まさか。
Don't tell me...
((ボクを思ってくれる人が
いるところが ボクの帰る場所))
Where there's someone thinking of me,
that's where I go home to.
帰るべき場所ってのは
アイツらのとこかよ！
His place to return is...
with them?!
なめるな ドロガメ！
Don't underestimate me...
Muddy turtle!
紅蓮さん！
Guren!
((紅蓮 : この椿は
決して枯れはしない。
This camellia will never wither.
(私が死なないかぎりはな))
As long as I'm alive.
Guren...san...
(紅蓮)牛頭。
Gozu...!
What are you doing?!
Take Yuukimaru and...
get out of here!
紅蓮さん…。
Guren-san...
ボク 帰る所が見つかったんだ。
I figured out where to return home to.
お前…。
You...
ゴオッ！
なんじゃ… 動きが止まったぞ。
What?! The Three-Tails
has stopped moving.
まさか…。
It can't be...!
(ガマ吉)
アイツ 三尾をコントロールできるのか!?
He... can control the Three-Tails?!
(カカシ)何だ？
What?!
(ヤマト)カカシ先輩！
Kakashi-senpai!
あれは…。
That's...!
なんだと!?
What?!
《紅蓮 : あれは
三尾が現れた異空間!?
That's the dimension where
the Three-Tails appeared!
あれに飲み込まれたら…》
If we're swallowed by it...!
((大丈夫か？
Are you all right?
(あったかい))
So warm...
((幽鬼丸 : はい。
(紅蓮)お前 これは…))
Here!
You... This is...!
《紅蓮 : 幽鬼丸…》
Yuukimaru...!
(紅蓮)
すべてのチャクラを この術に…。
All my Chakra is going to this Jutsu...!
今度は
ボクが手を握っててあげる…。
This time, I'll hold your hand...
Oh my god! Oh my god!
oh my god oh my god
yesterday's mistake got me discouraged, but
kinou no shippai de kojiketatte
Thank you! Thank you!
gottsuanda gottsuanda
my new clothes got splashed with some sauce, wow
onyuu no fuku ni sousu ga hanete wao
don't mind, don't mind, if I stay feeling like this I'll have a tear in my eyes
donmai donmai shizunda mama ja namida mo my eyes
I may be hungry and angry
donna ni hangurii de angurii demo
but I'll grab a bowl to eat and start dancing!
donburi kutte danshingu
We'll always be pals my brother!
orera itsumo demo nakama daro burazaa
hit me with an upwind or strong wind or a storm I'm ready so come on!
tatoe gyarufuu kyoufuu arashi ga fuitemo bacchikoi kamon
we may be apart but we'll still be under the same sky
hanaretetemo onaji sora no shita de
so smile and hang on
saa waratte funbatte
lets do it do it do it do it
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
even if morning doesn't come, yay yay
tatoe asa ga konakutatte yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
we'll still watch the dream together, yay yay
kimi to tomo ni yume wo miru ze yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
no matter what, don't ever, ever give up, yay yay
nani ga nandemo aa demo kou demo akirameru na yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
morning will always come after night, yay yay
donna yoru mo asa wa kuru ze yay yay
nanananana
へ～ 知らなかった。
Next Episode
I heard that the Three-Tails disappeared
after the last Great War.
サイって 私たちより
一つ年上なのね。
ゲジマユと一緒か…。
Orochimaru has gotten involved
with something troubling.
うわっ！ ヤマト隊長って
あれで 26歳!?
Perhaps the fact
that we discovered it first
えっ！ あんなオヤジ顔なのに…。
is a blessing in disguise.
趣味は 建築関係の本を読むこと。
Yes... We cannot hand it over to anyone.
うわ… 暗えな…。
We'll capture it then?
えっ？
I don't think it will be easy...
ハハッ！ 隊長と イルカ先生って
同い歳だぜ。
I'm going to look it up
in our existing documents.
I want you to summon these members.
ホントだ。 やだ…
趣味は 湯治って…。
Next Time: "Inside the Mist"
Inside the Mist
ギャハハ… まるで ジジイだな。
Huh? I didn't know...
Sai is one year older than us, huh?
ところで サクラちゃん 知ってた？
シズネのねえちゃん 31だぜ。
That makes him the same
as Bushy Brow, eh?
Wow! You mean Captain Yamato
looks like that, and he's only 26?!
えっ それは… 思ったより…。
Huh?! With those old looks?
だろ だろ… そうなると あの➡
アヒィ～っていうリアクション
ムリしすぎじゃねえ？
His hobby is
"reading books on architecture".
Ugh! How gloomy...
シ… シズネのねえちゃん!!
Huh?
(シズネ)今の話
もう一度 聞きたいな。
The Captain and Iruka-sensei
are the same age.
You're right...
フッ！
アヒィ～!!
Oh my, says here his hobby is
"medicinal hot spas".
He's like a totally old dude.
By the way, did you know, Sakura-chan?
Shizune nee-chan's 31.
Huh? That's older than I thought...
Right? Right?
Which means that "ahii!" reaction
has to be forced, right?
Sh-Shizune nee-chan!
I would like to hear that one more time...
Ahii!